[
    {
        "question": "What was the highest closing price for IBM in the data provided?",
        "answer": "$134.9400 on September 29, 2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest opening price for IBM in the data provided?",
        "answer": "$84.5000 on January 31, 2001"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which month had the highest trading volume in the data provided?",
        "answer": "March 30, 2001 with a volume of 254,550,000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which month had the highest high price, and what was that price?",
        "answer": "September 29, 2000 with a high of $134.9400"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the average closing price for IBM from the data provided?",
        "answer": "$111.82"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did the closing price surpass $200?",
        "answer": "0 times"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the total volume traded over the entire data period?",
        "answer": "3,396,314,300"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which months did IBM 2019s closing price decrease compared to the previous month?",
        "answer": "April 30, 2001, and May 31, 2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the range (difference between the high and low prices) for February 2005?",
        "answer": "$6.5400"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price in May 2000?",
        "answer": "$112.5000"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which month had the lowest closing price in the data provided?",
        "answer": "$85.0000 on December 29, 2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did the volume exceed 100 million?",
        "answer": "15 times"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest volume recorded in the data?",
        "answer": "254,550,000 on March 30, 2001"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the average high price for IBM from the data provided?",
        "answer": "$116.76"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which month had the lowest low price?",
        "answer": "$80.0600 on December 29, 2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price in March 2000?",
        "answer": "$118.3700"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which month had the highest closing price in 2000?",
        "answer": "$134.9400 on September 29, 2000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the high price in June 2000?",
        "answer": "$122.3100"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the closing price change from July 2000 to August 2000?",
        "answer": "The closing price increased from $112.2500 in July to $132.0200 in August"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the low price in January 2001?",
        "answer": "$83.7500"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of the article titled 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Summarize the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '.",
        "answer": "Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway reshuffles its portfolio, maintaining a strong grip on Apple shares. Buffett's latest moves stir curiosity ahead of his much-anticipated annual letter to investors."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stocks are mentioned in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "DMPZF, AAPL, C, ULTA, BAC, BRK-A, STZ, COF, DPZ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of DMPZF in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AAPL in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of C in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of ULTA in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of BAC in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of BRK-A in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of STZ in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of COF in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of DPZ in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What topics are covered in the article 'Berkshire Hathaway Adjusts Portfolio, Keeps Apple Stake Unchanged, Offloads Stakes in BofA - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Bank of America  ( NYSE:BAC ) '?",
        "answer": "Retail & Wholesale, Financial Markets, Manufacturing, Earnings, Technology, Finance"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of the article titled 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Summarize the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '.",
        "answer": "Benzinga examined the prospects for many investors' favorite stocks over the last week - here's a look at some of our top stories. The S&P 500 rose about 1.5% this week, while the Dow gained 0.6% and the Nasdaq climbed 2.6%."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stocks are mentioned in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "AA, NFLX, NVDA, AAPL, AVGO, CENX, SBUX, X, CLF, TSM, CRYPTO:DOGE"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AA in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of NFLX in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of NVDA in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AAPL in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AVGO in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of CENX in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of SBUX in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bearish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of X in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of CLF in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of TSM in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of CRYPTO:DOGE in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What topics are covered in the article 'Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 Bulls and Bears: Apple, Nvidia, Netflix and Trader Predicts Dogecoin Surge by March 24 - Alcoa  ( NYSE:AA ) '?",
        "answer": "Energy & Transportation, Technology, Economy - Monetary, Retail & Wholesale, Financial Markets, Manufacturing, Earnings"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of the article titled 'Steve Jobs-Signed Rare Apple Business Card Goes Up For Auction, Bids Touch $75,000'?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Summarize the article 'Steve Jobs-Signed Rare Apple Business Card Goes Up For Auction, Bids Touch $75,000'.",
        "answer": "A rare business card signed by late Apple Inc. co-founder Steve Jobs is drawing significant attention at an ongoing auction. What Happened: This unique piece of memorabilia, dating back to 1983, features Jobs's signature alongside the iconic Apple rainbow logo."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stocks are mentioned in the article 'Steve Jobs-Signed Rare Apple Business Card Goes Up For Auction, Bids Touch $75,000'?",
        "answer": "AAPL"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AAPL in the article 'Steve Jobs-Signed Rare Apple Business Card Goes Up For Auction, Bids Touch $75,000'?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What topics are covered in the article 'Steve Jobs-Signed Rare Apple Business Card Goes Up For Auction, Bids Touch $75,000'?",
        "answer": "Technology, Financial Markets"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of the article titled 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "Summarize the article 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '.",
        "answer": "Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft Corp. MSFT, expressed regret over leaving Harvard University to start the tech giant. What Happened: Gates, who was a Harvard undergraduate at the time, struggled with the decision to leave school despite having a great time there, according to a CNBC report."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stocks are mentioned in the article 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '?",
        "answer": "MSFT, AAPL, INTC"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of MSFT in the article 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AAPL in the article 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of INTC in the article 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bearish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What topics are covered in the article 'Bill Gates Wanted A Friend To 'Take Charge' Of Microsoft Due To Regret Over Leaving Harvard, But Here's Why He Panicked And Dropped Out - Microsoft  ( NASDAQ:MSFT ) , Intel  ( NASDAQ:INTC ) '?",
        "answer": "Technology, Manufacturing"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of the article titled 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Summarize the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '.",
        "answer": "Activist investor Dan Loeb's Third Point LLC has significantly ramped up its stakes in Flutter Entertainment FLUT, Elon Musk's Tesla Inc. TSLA, and Mark Zuckerberg's Meta Platforms Inc. META during the final quarter of 2024."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stocks are mentioned in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "MSFT, META, AAPL, TSLA, FLUT, AMZN"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of MSFT in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of META in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AAPL in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of TSLA in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of FLUT in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AMZN in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "question": "What topics are covered in the article 'Activist Investor Dan Loeb Boosts Stake In Mark Zuckerberg's Meta And Elon Musk's Tesla, But Sold These Three Mag 7 Stocks In Q4 - Apple  ( NASDAQ:AAPL ) , Amazon.com  ( NASDAQ:AMZN ) '?",
        "answer": "Retail & Wholesale, Financial Markets, Manufacturing, Mergers & Acquisitions, Technology"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of the article titled 'Surprise: McDonald's Has Higher Profit Margins Than Tesla, Apple, or Netflix'?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Summarize the article 'Surprise: McDonald's Has Higher Profit Margins Than Tesla, Apple, or Netflix'.",
        "answer": "Restaurants have notoriously low profit margins. But McDonald's ( NYSE: MCD ) , the world's largest restaurant chain, is surprisingly one of the most profitable businesses. In fact, its profit margins are higher than prestigious businesses such as Tesla ( NASDAQ: TSLA ) , Apple ( NASDAQ: AAPL ) , ..."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stocks are mentioned in the article 'Surprise: McDonald's Has Higher Profit Margins Than Tesla, Apple, or Netflix'?",
        "answer": "NFLX, AAPL, TSLA, MDNDF"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of NFLX in the article 'Surprise: McDonald's Has Higher Profit Margins Than Tesla, Apple, or Netflix'?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sentiment of AAPL in the article 'Surprise: McDonald's Has Higher Profit Margins Than Tesla, Apple, or Netflix'?",
        "answer": "Somewhat-Bullish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2025-02-14?",
        "answer": "$252.4000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2025-02-14?",
        "answer": "$265.7200"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2025-02-14?",
        "answer": "$246.8700"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2025-02-14?",
        "answer": "$261.2800"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2025-02-14?",
        "answer": "50047921"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2025-01-31?",
        "answer": "$221.8200"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2025-01-31?",
        "answer": "$261.8000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2025-01-31?",
        "answer": "$214.6100"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2025-01-31?",
        "answer": "$255.7000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2025-01-31?",
        "answer": "92424171"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-12-31?",
        "answer": "$227.5000"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-12-31?",
        "answer": "$239.3500"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-12-31?",
        "answer": "$217.6523"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-12-31?",
        "answer": "$219.8300"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-12-31?",
        "answer": "81535689"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-11-29?",
        "answer": "$207.7700"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-11-29?",
        "answer": "$230.3600"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-11-29?",
        "answer": "$204.0700"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-11-29?",
        "answer": "$227.4100"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-11-29?",
        "answer": "77280587"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-10-31?",
        "answer": "$220.6300"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-10-31?",
        "answer": "$237.3700"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-10-31?",
        "answer": "$203.5100"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-10-31?",
        "answer": "$206.7200"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-10-31?",
        "answer": "105624376"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-09-30?",
        "answer": "$201.9100"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-09-30?",
        "answer": "$224.1500"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-09-30?",
        "answer": "$199.3350"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-09-30?",
        "answer": "$221.0800"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-09-30?",
        "answer": "83415811"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-08-30?",
        "answer": "$192.8100"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-08-30?",
        "answer": "$202.1700"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-08-30?",
        "answer": "$181.8100"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-08-30?",
        "answer": "$202.1300"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-08-30?",
        "answer": "65453729"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-07-31?",
        "answer": "$173.4500"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-07-31?",
        "answer": "$196.2600"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-07-31?",
        "answer": "$173.3800"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-07-31?",
        "answer": "$192.1400"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-07-31?",
        "answer": "81258646"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-06-28?",
        "answer": "$166.5400"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-06-28?",
        "answer": "$178.4599"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-06-28?",
        "answer": "$163.5300"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-06-28?",
        "answer": "$172.9500"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-06-28?",
        "answer": "70706301"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the opening price of IBM in 2024-05-31?",
        "answer": "$165.6900"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the highest price IBM reached in 2024-05-31?",
        "answer": "$175.4600"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the lowest price IBM traded at in 2024-05-31?",
        "answer": "$162.6200"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the closing price of IBM in 2024-05-31?",
        "answer": "$166.8500"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the trading volume for IBM in 2024-05-31?",
        "answer": "78620355"
    }
]